filmofilia.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy - FilmoFilia

## Ownership of Information

FilmoFilia is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

## Comments

FilmoFilia website contain comment sections. We do not 100% actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

## Cookies

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

## Third Party Advertisers and cookies

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time via . For more details including access requests and complaints, review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com).

Exponential Cookie Details:

## Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

## Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but FilmoFilia may need to disclose information when required by law.

## Links

FilmoFilia website link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by FilmoFilia.

## Notification of Changes

When FilmoFilia makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Reproduction without explicit permission is prohibited. All Rights Reserved.**

## Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us: **filmofilia [at] gmail.com**

* * *

Filmofilia – movie website by FilmoFilia.com is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/).  
Based on a work at www.filmofilia.com.  
Permissions beyond the scope of this license may be available at <https://www.filmofilia.com/about/privacy-policy/>.

* * *
